chelseabridson

software developer

about

interests

435 N Fairview Ave Lansing, MI 48912 (517) 918 - 0717

material design, user experience, web accessibility, single page applications, mobile design, continuous integration and delivery, automated deployment, automated acceptance tests

✓ chelsea@bridson.me♣ chelsea.bridson.me♀ git://seadb

education

languages

native english basic spanish 12–2015

B.Sc. in Computer Science

Computer Science & Engineering

Dean's List, College of Engineering Scholarship

MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY

College of Engineering

2015-2016 Hacker Fello

HACKER FELLOWS

CISSP ASSOCIATE

Fellowship which matches developer talent with Michigan startups and includes

a 5-week entrepreneurship & coding bootcamp and stipend

2017 CISSP
Certified Information Systems Security Professional

programming

experience

2017

2015-2016

Javascript/ES6 •••••

React •••••

Redux ••••

Angular ••• jQuery •••

C/C++ •••

C# ••

Python ••

CSS3 •••••
HTML5 •••••

Node ••••

Django •••

SQL •••

2018-present 6 Liquid Web

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Collaborated on a team to create a new user interface for my.liquidweb.com
- Created UI mockups to confirm design meets business requirements
- Create and maintain an automated end-to-end test suite to cover basic acceptance criteria to verify business level requirements for manage.liquidweb.com
- Write and maintain thorough unit tests to ensure code reliability

TOOLS: REACT, REDUX, SKETCH, SELENIUM, PERL, JAVASCRIPT, GITLAB

 SECURITY ANALYST

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- Developed the WAMS internal firewall onboarding software
- Responded to support tickets and issued SSL certificates for internal servers

TOOLS: C#, ASP.NET, MICROSOFT SERVER, GIT

volunteering

2018 🗞 Lansing Bike Party

2017 🗱 Lansing Bike Co-op

2016 Room at the Inn Warming Center

2016 Food Gatherers

2015 🖍 Common Cycle

2014 ☐ MSU Women In Engineering

2013 & EL Hot Yoga

2013 The Giving Tree Farm

2012 Ronald McDonald House Mid-Michigan

Seelio

Skills Map

- Created a user-interface for the skills map, a feature designed to help students connect soft skills to past experiences and projects
- Researched and implemented continuous integration & deployment
- Adhered to Agile bi-weekly sprint planning sessions and daily

JAVASCRIPT, BACKBONE.JS, KNOCKOUT, CIRCLECI, SELENIUM, AWS, GIT